character remains a lot of content that is
personaje queda mucho contenido que es
that they do not want that content I am going to
que no quieren ese contenido voy a
advance one thing to see
adelantar una cosa a ver
this I mean it is not information to use
esto O sea no es información al uso
after several conversations it is something that
tras varias conversaciones es una cosa a
I have been
la que yo
able to glimpse maybe I could be
he podido entrever a lo mejor me puedo
wrong we save this live I think I think I
equivocar guardamos este directo
think that in a few
creo Creo Pienso que de aquí a unas
weeks there is another person who is going to be
semanas hay otra persona que va a estar
vetoed not fired because he does not work in
vetada no despedida porque no trabaja en
the network right now
la cadena ahora mismo
okay And it is a person about whom there is
vale Y es una persona de la que se habla
a lot of talk about that is
un montón
talked about a lot yes And it is
de la que se habla un montón sí Y es
Also I think that we are going to talk about her
Además creo que vamos a hablar de ella
now
ahora
and I think that her topic is going to be vetoed and
y creo que va a estar vetada su tema y
I do not know what they are going to do about that topic but
yo no sé qué van a hacer ese tema pero
but you mean Anabel Pantoja
pero te refieres Anabel Pantoja
no I think so yes from two
no yo creo que sí sí por dos
conversations that I have had with a
conversaciones que he tenido con una
person who works in the program and for
persona que trabaja en el programa y por
things because yes because yes maybe
cosas que porque sí porque sí a lo mejor
I am wrong but I think that
me equivoco pero creo que se va a vetar
this topic is going to be vetoed because I think that it is not in their interest
ese tema porque creo que no les interesa
And it is not because Beyond what
Y no es porque Más allá de lo que haya
Anabel has said that
dicho Anabel que se puede plantear
some type of measure can be considered to stop
tomarme algún tipo de medida para frenar
this attack of sálvame because we already know
este ataque de sálvame porque ya sabemos
that sálvame is also with me against me
que sálvame también es conmigo contra mí
Anabel has refused to work There she has
Anabel se ha negado a trabajar Ahí se ha
refused to give them gas and when you
negado a darles gasolina y cuando Te
refuse they come after you then Anabel Now
niegas van a por ti entonces Anabel Ya
mom won't keep quiet anymore so mom has
mamá ya no se calla entonces mamá se ha
rebelled a little bit and I don't know to what
revelado un poquito y no sé hasta qué
extent or in the factory or Serena saves
punto o en la fábrica o salva de Serena
or maybe they are considering
o a lo mejor se plantean
from above having to give them a notice
desde arriba tener que darles un toque
saying you can't talk about
de decir no podéis volver a hablar de
this person again
esta persona
because the program that she is preparing
porque el programa que está preparando
with only Anabel Pantoja is not for
con único Anabel Pantoja no es para
Telecinco but for Amazon, let's
telecinco sino para Amazon
see this is for older I spoke with let's
es que a ver esto es de mayor hablé con
see on Anabel's trips it's that
a ver en los viajes de Anabel es que
well she hasn't given in either she
bueno ella tampoco ella ha concedido
is now at a press conference
ahora está en una rueda de prensa
today
hoy
and she also doesn't show that she is going to
y ella tampoco se nota que ya lo va a
announce it in a few days it is clear that she ca
anunciar en unos días se nota que
n't make much progress but what she
tampoco puede avanzar mucho pero ya lo
has said about the subject of Anabelle's trips
que ha contado del tema de los viajes de
that the fact that they give her a
Anabelle que el hecho que le den un
program
programa
Who said it is for Amazon has already
Quién ha dicho que es para Amazon lo ha
confirmed it that it is for Amazon in the
confirmado ya que es para Amazon al
end I am going to tell you a Twitter account
final te lo voy a decir una cuenta de
who Look, let's go I don't know if this will be the
quién Mira vamos no sé si será esta la
first Twitter account that has
primera cuenta de Twitter que la ha
put it but I think it is the same
puesto pero es que creo que es la misma
Twitter account  who said that about
cuenta de Twitter que dijo lo de
no What a laugh I get with this I'm very
no Qué risa con esta me llevo Yo muy
good it's Encarna Sánchez not the one from Encarna
bien es Encarna Sánchez no la de Encarna
Sánchez I'm cracking up with her tweets no no I don't know
Sánchez Me parto con sus tweet no no no
I don't know I don't know if she
sé no sé creo que yo no sé si ha
confirmed the Amazon thing I think
confirmado lo de Amazon yo creo que yo
because of who I've spoken to The thing is that I was
por con quién he hablado La cosa es que
going to go within Mediaset it was not known
iba a ir dentro de mediaset no se sabía
if to Four to Telecinco that in the case
si a cuatro a telecinco que en el caso
that Telecinco went to save me
de que fueran telecinco a salvarme se le
the deal was over you can't apart from that it
acabó el chollo no puedes aparte que lo
was in the ethical code although she doesn't
ponía en el código ético aunque ella da
care you can't attack or criticize
igual tú no puedes atacar o criticar a
someone it's the same as when when they
alguien es igual que cuando cuando
talked about Paula Echeverría she was looking
hablaban de Paula Echeverría buscaba
before the separation Paula was already being put in a
ante la separación ya Paula la ponían a
bad light when Paula entered
caldo cuando Paula entró en
where she worked within Telecinco
donde trabajaba dentro de telecinco
before voting she entered a series that
antes de votar entró en una serie que
would be 35 And she had to do
sería de 35 Y tuvo que hacer ahí
promotion there their deal was cut off and
promoción se les cortó el chollo y
speaking well of Paula you can't
hablar bien de Paula tú no puedes
generate a program in Mediaset Anabelle
generar un programa en mediaset Anabelle
and put the deal save me while in
y poner la caldo sálvame mientras en
Four there are Anabelle's trips and
cuatro están los viajes de Anabelle y
because it doesn't make sense and apart from that it's not
porque no tiene sentido y aparte no es
an interview program as such but rather it
un programa de entrevistas como tal sino
's more like  for her beloved
que es más bien por las sus queridas
Canary Islands for the places Canabel you don't
Canarias por los sitios canabel no
know her trips it's not for
conoces sus viajes no es tampoco de
interviews but rather trips with friends
entrevista sino pues viajes con amigos
to El Hierro to La Gomera here and there It's
al hierro a la gomera para acá para allá
a little bit of Anabelle what people
Es un poco pues Anabelle lo que la gente
like that is Anabel seeing Anabel
le gusta que es Anabel ver Anabel
natural Anabelle makes mistakes
natural Anabelle hace de equivocarse
Anabel say a swear word Ana or rather it's more the
Anabel decir un taco Ana o sea es más la
essence of Anabel I think I don't know if it
esencia de Anabel yo creo yo no sé si
will work at this point maybe yes it
funcionará a estas alturas a lo mejor sí
could be that if I don't know but
puede ser que si no lo sé pero
but
pero
no don't call me like that I speak suddenly maybe
que no no me llamas así hablo de pronto
Then we'll see it and We say the
a lo mejor Luego lo vemos y Decimos lo
opposite but this suddenly it doesn't seem very very
contrario pero así de pronto no se me
appetizing to me no but I tell you
muy apetitoso no pero yo te digo
remember this I think that from now on
acordaos de esto yo creo que de aquí a
Not much longer The fun of talking about
No mucho Se acabó el chollo de hablar de
Anabelle is over and what was missing
Anabelle y ya lo que faltaba
[Music]
[Música]